Guide to the School of Electrical and Computer Engineering records, 1959-2007.
School of Electrical and Computer Engineering records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Electrical and Computer Engineering records, 1959-2007.
16-6-2731
Cornell University.School of Electrical and Computer Engineering.
1 item and 4 cubic feet.
Manuscripts, Publications, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes meeting minutes and memoranda, annual reports, and faculty meeting minutes.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Laser-generated hologram paperweight designed by Simpson Linke meant to serve as a memento for individuals who have rendered distinguished service to the School of Electrical Engineering.
Includes meeting minutes and memoranda concerning the centennial in 1985, annual reports from 1980-1987 and faculty meeting minutes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Linke, Simpson.
Subjects:
Electrical engineering--Study and teaching.; Electrical engineering--History.; Electrical engineering--Exhibitions.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin: Box 2
SERIES LIST
Series I. ECE Hologram Paperweight
Series II. Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes
Series III. Faculty Meeting Minutes
Series IV. Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes
Series V. Policy Committee
Series VI. School of Electrical and Computer Engineering Centennial
Series VII. Department Annual Reports and Other Reports
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. ECE Hologram Paperweight
  - Hologram Paperweight For Distinguished Service to the School of Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box 1)
- Series II. Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, September 1945-June 1947 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, September 1947-November 1950 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, November 1951-November 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, January 1953-June 1954 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, 1954-June 1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, September 1958-June 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, September 1960-May 1961 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, October 1961-June 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, October 1964-April 1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, May 1965-June 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, September 1966-October 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, January 1969-November 1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - ECE Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, September 1970-March 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Series III. Faculty Meeting Minutes
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, December 1964-October 1955 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, September 1960-December 1963 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, January 1964-May 1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, April 1967-December 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, May 1971-May 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, October 1972-May 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, September 1973-June 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, August 1974-June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1975-June 1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1976-June 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1977-June 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1996-June 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ECE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Series IV. Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes
  - ECE Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, February 1958-November 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - ECE Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, January 1967-June 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - ECE Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, April 1971-May 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ECE Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, September 1974-June 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - ECE Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, July 1981-June 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series V. Policy Committee
  - Policy Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Policy Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Policy Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Policy Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Policy Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Policy Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Policy Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Policy Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Policy Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Policy Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Policy Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Policy Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Policy Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Policy Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Policy Committee, July 1988-June 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Policy Committee, April 1989-May 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Policy Committee, July 1991-June 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Policy Committee, July 1993-June 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Policy Committee, July 1995-June 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Policy Committee, July 1996-June 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Policy Committee, July 1998-October 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Series VI. School of Electrical and Computer Engineering Centennial
  - Centennial Planning Material (1), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Planning Material (2), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Planning Material (3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Series VII. Department Annual Reports and Other Reports
  - Annual Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report (Appendices), 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report (Published Papers, Conferences, Seminars, Etc.), 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report (Research), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - IEEE International Symposium on Information Theory Paper Abstracts, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report (Appendices), 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Profiles, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 5)
  - Report on Microwave Electronics Activities prepared by Lester Eastman, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Report on Microwave Electronics Activities prepared by Lester Eastman, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Brochure of Graduate Studies in Microwave Electronics, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York State Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project- Self-Study Questionnaire Statewide Review, June 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Series VIII. Photographs
  - Photocopy of Photograph of Senior Class in the School of Electrical Engineering, June 1945 (Box 8, Folder 8)